Come on, get on up.
-- 來吧，站起來
We're wild and we can't be tamed.
-- 展現野性，拒絕豢養
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
We live in a crazy world.
-- 同生在這癲狂世界
Caught up in a rat race
-- 在各種競爭中相遇
concrete jungle life. is sometimes a mad place.
-- 活在鋼筋水泥叢林下,有時特別燥亂
It's you and me together. at the end of a wild day.
-- 狂野一天之後, 我們又在一起
Don't keep it all bottled up
-- 別總是悶在心裡
and release your energy.
-- 綻放你的熱情
Only reason we are here is to celebrate
-- 你我同在這，只為大玩一場
in a place where anyone can be anything.
-- 就在此地，天馬行空隨你發揮
Hold on to this moment. Don't let it fade away.
-- 盡情享受當下，別錯過任何一刻
Baby, keep the music playing.
-- 寶貝，音樂繼續進行下去
Come on, get on up.
-- 來吧，站起來
We wild and we can't be tamed.
-- 展現野性，拒絕豢養
And we turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
Come on, keep it up.
-- 來吧，振作起來
It's fun if you're down to play
-- 加入遊戲，歡樂加倍
and we turn the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
We're living in a heat of time.
-- 生活在這激烈時代
No chance to cool down.
-- 少有機會放慢步調
Continunously confined and what do we do now?
-- 受環境所限，該如何才能突破
It's all about finding love. sometimes hard to come by
-- 重於尋找愛情,有時難能可貴
But when it comes to us,
-- 但若愛人到來
it's always a good time.
-- 必定幸福美滿
only reason we are here is to celebrate.
-- 你我同在這，只為大玩一場
In a place where anyone can be anything.
-- 就在此地，天馬行空隨你發揮
Hold on to this moment. Don't let it fade away.
-- 盡情享受當下，別錯過任何一刻
Baby, keep the music playing.
-- 寶貝，音樂繼續進行下去
Come on, get on up.
-- 來吧，站起來
We're wild and we can't be tamed.
-- 展現野性，拒絕豢養
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
It's fun if you're down to play
-- 加入遊戲，歡樂加倍
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
I'll take you higher.
-- 我會帶你向上
I'll take you higher and we can't be tamed. baby
-- 我會帶你向上,拒絕豢養
I'll take you higher.
-- 我們一起向上
I'll take you higher. I'll take you higher
and we can't be tamed.
-- 拒絕豢養
take you higher
-- 我們一起向上
Es una fiesta
-- 派對狂熱
que sube como la espuma
-- 如泡沫般一路飆升
Yo por ti ire hasta la luna
-- 為了你 我願意
de ida y vuelta
-- 來回奔波月球
Es una fiesta
-- 派對狂熱
que sube como la espuma
-- 如泡沫般一路飆升
Yo por ti ire hasta la luna
-- 為了你 我願意
de ida y vuelta
-- 來回奔波月球
Come on, get on up.
-- 來吧，站起來
We're wild and we can't be tamed.
-- 拒絕豢養
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
Come on, get on up.
-- 來吧，站起來
We're wild and we can't be tamed.
-- 展現野性，拒絕豢養
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
Come on, get on up.
-- 來吧，站起來
It's fun if you're down to play
-- 加入遊戲，歡樂加倍
And we're turning the floor into a zoo.
-- 把這邊變成我們專屬的動物園
--